{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Junction Field Effect Transistors (JFET) contain how many diodes?", "opta": "4", "optb": "3", "optc": "2", "optd": "1", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an input delta of 2 V produces a transconductance of 1.5 mS, what is the drain current delta?", "opta": "666 mA", "optb": "3 mA", "optc": "0.75 mA", "optd": "0.5 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When not in use, MOSFET pins are kept at the same potential through the use of:", "opta": "shipping foil", "optb": "nonconductive foam", "optc": "conductive foam", "optd": "a wrist strap", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "D-MOSFETs are sometimes used in series to construct a cascode high-frequency amplifier to overcome the loss of:", "opta": "low output impedance", "optb": "capacitive reactance", "optc": "high input impedance", "optd": "inductive reactance", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A \"U\" shaped, opposite-polarity material built near a JFET-channel center is called the:", "opta": "gate", "optb": "block", "optc": "drain", "optd": "heat sink", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When testing an n-channel D-MOSFET, resistance G to D = , resistance G to S = , resistance D to SS =  and 500 , depending on the polarity of the ohmmeter, and resistance D to S = 500 . What is wrong?", "opta": "short D to S", "optb": "open G to D", "optc": "open D to SS", "optd": "nothing", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the constant-current region, how will the IDS change in an n-channel JFET?", "opta": "As VGS decreases ID decreases.", "optb": "As VGS increases ID increases.", "optc": "As VGS decreases ID remains constant.", "optd": "As VGS increases ID remains constant.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A MOSFET has how many terminals?", "opta": "2 or 3", "optb": "3", "optc": "4", "optd": "3 or 4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IDSS can be defined as:", "opta": "the minimum possible drain current", "optb": "the maximum possible current with VGS held at \u20134 V", "optc": "the maximum possible current with VGS held at 0 V", "optd": "the maximum drain current with the source shorted", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the input impedance of a common-gate configured JFET?", "opta": "very low", "optb": "low", "optc": "high", "optd": "very high", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "JFET terminal \"legs\" are connections to the drain, the gate, and the:", "opta": "channel", "optb": "source", "optc": "substrate", "optd": "cathode", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A very simple bias for a D-MOSFET is called:", "opta": "self biasing", "optb": "gate biasing", "optc": "zero biasing", "optd": "voltage-divider biasing", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With the E-MOSFET, when gate input voltage is zero, drain current is:", "opta": "at saturation", "optb": "zero", "optc": "IDSS", "optd": "widening the channel", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With a 30-volt VDD, and an 8-kilohm drain resistor, what is the E-MOSFET Q point voltage, with ID = 3 mA?", "opta": "6 V", "optb": "10 V", "optc": "24 V", "optd": "30 V", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an input signal reduces the channel size, the process is called:", "opta": "enhancement", "optb": "substrate connecting", "optc": "gate charge", "optd": "depletion", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which JFET configuration would connect a high-resistance signal source to a low-resistance load?", "opta": "source follower", "optb": "common-source", "optc": "common-drain", "optd": "common-gate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How will electrons flow through a p-channel JFET?", "opta": "from source to drain", "optb": "from source to gate", "optc": "from drain to gate", "optd": "from drain to source", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When VGS = 0 V, a JFET is:", "opta": "saturated", "optb": "an analog device", "optc": "an open switch", "optd": "cut off", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When applied input voltage varies the resistance of a channel, the result is called:", "opta": "saturization", "optb": "polarization", "optc": "cutoff", "optd": "field effect", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When is a vertical channel E-MOSFET used?", "opta": "for high frequencies", "optb": "for high voltages", "optc": "for high currents", "optd": "for high resistances", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When the JFET is no longer able to control the current, this point is called the:", "opta": "breakdown region", "optb": "depletion region", "optc": "saturation point", "optd": "pinch-off region", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "With a JFET, a ratio of output current change against an input voltage change is called:", "opta": "transconductance", "optb": "siemens", "optc": "resistivity", "optd": "gain", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of JFET bias requires a negative supply voltage?", "opta": "feedback", "optb": "source", "optc": "gate", "optd": "voltage divider", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How will a D-MOSFET input impedance change with signal frequency?", "opta": "As frequency increases input impedance increases.", "optb": "As frequency increases input impedance is constant.", "optc": "As frequency decreases input impedance increases.", "optd": "As frequency decreases input impedance is constant.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The type of bias most often used with E-MOSFET circuits is:", "opta": "constant current", "optb": "drain-feedback", "optc": "voltage-divider", "optd": "zero biasing", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The transconductance curve of a JFET is a graph of:", "opta": "IS versus VDS", "optb": "IC versus VCE", "optc": "ID versus VGS", "optd": "ID \u00d7 RDS", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The common-source JFET amplifier has:", "opta": "a very high input impedance and a relatively low voltage gain", "optb": "a high input impedance and a very high voltage gain", "optc": "a high input impedance and a voltage gain less than 1", "optd": "no voltage gain", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using voltage-divider biasing, what is the voltage at the gate VGS?", "opta": "5.2 V", "optb": "4.2 V", "optc": "3.2 V", "optd": "2.2 V", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The overall input capacitance of a dual-gate D-MOSFET is lower because the devices are usually connected:", "opta": "in parallel", "optb": "with separate insulation", "optc": "with separate inputs", "optd": "in series", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the transconductance of an FET when ID = 1 mA and VGS = 1 V?", "opta": "1 kS", "optb": "1 mS", "optc": "1 k", "optd": "1 m", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which component is considered to be an \"OFF\" device?", "opta": "transistor", "optb": "JFET", "optc": "D-MOSFET", "optd": "E-MOSFET", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In an n-channel JFET, what will happen at the pinch-off voltage?", "opta": "the value of VDS at which further increases in VDS will cause no further increase in ID", "optb": "the value of VGS at which further decreases in VGS will cause no further increases in ID", "optc": "the value of VDG at which further decreases in VDG will cause no further increases in ID", "optd": "the value of VDS at which further increases in VGS will cause no further increases in ID", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}